{
    "subject": "resource/Double_Dragon",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Techn\u014ds_Japan_beat_'em_ups",
    "human_readable": "The subject of Double Dragon is Category:Techn\u014ds Japan beat 'em ups.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8181977272033691,
            "question": "What makes Double Dragon a classic beat 'em up game?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7459573745727539,
            "question": "What genre is Double Dragon classified as?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7146587371826172,
            "question": "What are some common elements found in beat 'em up games like Double Dragon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6562525033950806,
            "question": "What type of game is Double Dragon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5794157385826111,
            "question": "Which company developed Double Dragon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48245248198509216,
            "question": "Where is Techn\u014ds Japan based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4610520005226135,
            "question": "Is Double Dragon a fighting game?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44213542342185974,
            "question": "What is the primary gameplay style in Double Dragon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37612584233283997,
            "question": "Are there any other popular games by Techn\u014ds Japan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3587283194065094,
            "question": "What era did Double Dragon originate from?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of Double Dragon is Category:Techn\u014ds Japan beat 'em ups.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6122_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other popular games by Techn\u014ds Japan?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6122_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the primary gameplay style in Double Dragon?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6122_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Double Dragon a fighting game?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6122_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6122_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6122_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6122_137.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6122_138.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6122_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6122_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6122_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6122_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6122_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6122_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the Double Dragon series, which are indeed Techn\u014ds Japan beat 'em ups. Therefore, the statement \"The subject of Double Dragon is Category:Techn\u014ds Japan beat 'em ups\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}